<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>🐢 ka cheesy blog</title>
    <link>https://ghateAditya.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on 🐢 ka cheesy blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 13 Feb 2023 21:35:48 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://ghateAditya.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>The Vulnerability</title>
      <link>https://ghateAditya.github.io/posts/the_vulnerability/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Feb 2023 21:35:48 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ghateAditya.github.io/posts/the_vulnerability/</guid>
      <description>Uff, 13th Feb it is. One day before launch and still a bunch of logistics to figure out. But I think I will get it done in time. I just wish all of this effort brings up atleast a smile on your face. If I am able to pass through the tough shell even for a second, then all of this will be worth it. Squishmallow should be arriving tomorrow and google nest hub was a hit.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Homeostasis</title>
      <link>https://ghateAditya.github.io/posts/the_homeostatis/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Feb 2023 22:10:33 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ghateAditya.github.io/posts/the_homeostatis/</guid>
      <description>Its been 22 days since I last saw you. And 54 days since I heard an &amp;ldquo;I love you&amp;rdquo; back. A lot changed, yet everything remained the same. There were a lot of changes to navigate and get used to, but my partner through this journey remained familiar. When things are in natural equilibrium or have been done the same way for a long time, it becomes easy to not appreciate the small things.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Vows</title>
      <link>https://ghateAditya.github.io/posts/the_promise/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Feb 2023 21:42:32 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ghateAditya.github.io/posts/the_promise/</guid>
      <description>Valentine&amp;rsquo;s day is right around the corner. So a final few days and a lot of things to do. I have to fix the layout, check how the website looks on mobile, add photos and edit the posts. I missed my streak and couldn&amp;rsquo;t write a post yesterday. Just took a paracetamol and slept. But enough of that. Throughout the course of these posts I have moved from what happened in the past to how it is now in the present.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Space</title>
      <link>https://ghateAditya.github.io/posts/the_space/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Feb 2023 22:10:57 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ghateAditya.github.io/posts/the_space/</guid>
      <description>Wohooo, day 9 of showering all my love into words. Well not all of it. You cannot quantify a reservoir. Its endless. But if I had to throw numbers at you, then 14. I left you 14 reels ka syllabus to look at before coming in to type this. I like to think tu dekhti to hogi atleast, even when you don&amp;rsquo;t reply. I like to think you care, even when you don&amp;rsquo;t show it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Wait</title>
      <link>https://ghateAditya.github.io/posts/the_wait/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Feb 2023 10:52:46 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ghateAditya.github.io/posts/the_wait/</guid>
      <description>They say good things come to those who wait. Maybe it is true. But waiting is not easy. It tests your patience and resilience like anything. But wait turns painful when it is associated with a person whom you love. And I am not blaming the person who we are waiting for, but you understand what longing for someone&amp;rsquo;s love and attention means. And then you start seeking it in different ways.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Perfect Boyfriend</title>
      <link>https://ghateAditya.github.io/posts/the_perfect_boyfriend/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Feb 2023 22:44:08 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ghateAditya.github.io/posts/the_perfect_boyfriend/</guid>
      <description>Everyone loves the idea of perfectionism. People have set high standards for themselves. Even in relationships. I get that feeling. Because I always wanted to be the perfect boyfriend. I wanted to be the solution for all your problems. To help you in all possible ways, to be there for you through all of your moods and just be there with a fix when you hit a blocker. And to a point I succeeded in doing so.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Love Language</title>
      <link>https://ghateAditya.github.io/posts/the_love_language/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Feb 2023 22:41:27 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ghateAditya.github.io/posts/the_love_language/</guid>
      <description>I learnt about something called a love language. Turns out every individual has a specific love language that they speak. It is their own way of expressing love for their partner. Understanding each other&amp;rsquo;s love language becomes important to know how your partner exprsses their love and vice versa. This was new information for me because I understood both of our ways to express love are different. And for a long time I used to get sad when you didn&amp;rsquo;t express yourself or say things out loud.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Resolve</title>
      <link>https://ghateAditya.github.io/posts/the_resolve/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Feb 2023 22:11:06 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ghateAditya.github.io/posts/the_resolve/</guid>
      <description>Holistically everything functions in cycles and patterns. Bad times have to be followed by good times, just like dawn after dusk. This perpetual cycle signifies flux in the way of the world, that good times will evetually be followed by the bad days and this is inevitable. Acceptance and learning to handle both the good and bad is all that is in our control. We went through a nightmare, and I can only hope we&amp;rsquo;re moving towards a glorious sunrise, stronger than ever.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Pain</title>
      <link>https://ghateAditya.github.io/posts/the_pain/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Feb 2023 22:21:38 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ghateAditya.github.io/posts/the_pain/</guid>
      <description>I had originally decided I would write one post every day for the next 14 days, but today was a day I could not focus on anything else. I started off my day remembering my presence was not wanted just because I was high. And it felt really bad. Because it was a simple thing I asked. And to be said no, worst of all listening to the explanation that you could not deal with me right now.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Battle Within</title>
      <link>https://ghateAditya.github.io/posts/the_battle_within/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Feb 2023 21:34:41 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ghateAditya.github.io/posts/the_battle_within/</guid>
      <description>Thoughts shape the world within and beyond. Pretty heavy statement to make, but I can back it up. You live in a world that your mind perceives. And your version of reality might be different than the actual. You are what your thoughts make you believe, and your thoughts are responsible for the way you interact with others and shape their version of reality. Thoughts affect mood, health and almost everything.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Reality Check</title>
      <link>https://ghateAditya.github.io/posts/the_reality_check/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Feb 2023 19:29:22 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ghateAditya.github.io/posts/the_reality_check/</guid>
      <description>Do you know that feeling when you get a new idea and think this is totally possible? And on the next day you realise you took on a lot more than you can chew. That building a blog in 14 days looks fancy but won&amp;rsquo;t be easy. But I like this feeling of idealism at this age. That anything is possible. Everything should just be a time problem. This feeling is what drives me and right now this looks like a big project, but its a good problem to have.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The beginning</title>
      <link>https://ghateAditya.github.io/posts/the_beginning/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Feb 2023 22:06:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ghateAditya.github.io/posts/the_beginning/</guid>
      <description>Funny story, well doesn&amp;rsquo;t sound funny at all right now but I hope it will later on. THe exact moment I started writing this you cut your hand while cutting onions. If I had to say this is a sign, the moment I thought I need to up my game for Valentine&amp;rsquo;s day, it had to be marked by blood. But red is the colour of love, so overall a great muhurt to begin!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
